Do we have any golfers in here right now?
Come on, golfing enthusiasts.
Stand up and make some noise.
Now, if you're a golfer who loves to hit on the cart girl,
keep making noise and please, for the love of God,
check yourself in the Arkham Asylum ASAP.
He's nothing.
I am being dangerous.
You do recognize that you're absolutely stunning, right?
I just saw this golden nugget here today
and I've got to show you perhaps the most aggressive
and most inefficient ris
is ever captured on camera.
Now, to briefly explain what a cart girl is
to those who might not know,
it's an employee of the golf course
who rides around in what's fundamentally an ambulance
for people that are really hungry or thirsty on the course.
They bring a bunch of likes, snacks and stuff
so that way you can purchase them to re-energize.
Well, this gentle sur here after tipping a fedora decides
that he wanted a little more than refreshments
from the cart girl this time around.
So I don't know exactly what led to it,
but you can see in the beginning, he said,
please don't thank me and then goes to say that
and then goes on to say that I'm being dangerous.
So I have to imagine it went like this.
She approaches in the cart and says,
hey, sir, do you need beverages?
And he's like, I'm being dangerous.
You're beautiful.
What's men?
I would imagine most men, especially of an older generation,
they're not used to seem such a parent beauty.
Not when they see someone just as breathtaking as you.
He is a wonderful thing to find someone attractive
and then to have their attention.
Brother, you don't have her attention.
You have her held hostage.
She is working.
She is obligated to interact with you
and you also have your entire arm
on the steering wheel of the golf cart.
She couldn't leave even if she made a mad dash
to try and get out of there, peddled to the metal.
He has got her trapped in his spider web here,
locked into this cutscene that she can't skip.
I also hate the way he talks.
He talks like a pinky up old school redditor
gloating about understanding a Rick and Morty joke.
Like he talks like he's giving some kind of self-help speech.
It's so annoying.
It's just the way he goes on.
Like it's like a drama club,
thespian troop type monologue that he gives here.
And it also doesn't make any sense.
Like what do you mean most older men
probably haven't seen beauty like her?
Wouldn't older men have been exposed to more beauty
because they've been around longer?
What, just because this guy watches porn or something?
He thinks like old men must not have seen what I've seen.
I understand how to handle myself
around attractive women.
I consume porn.
For however fleeting it may be.
And so for me, I as a man,
to see someone else stunning as you, it is exhilarating.
So imagine being in your presence,
being in your orbit, these older gentlemen
who have never seen such beauty.
I would imagine that they are just
taking so back that they become monkeys,
like most men are,
or into understanding why I feel what I feel.
I don't know why he's so aggressively yelling at her.
You're stunning.
And they also take these long pauses.
I would imagine your beauty takes older men
and reduces them to primates.
Not like me, not like me.
You see, I can understand your beauty.
The duff has tingled my very soul.
It is exhilarating.
Exquisite.
Even the subtle vicissitudes of love, blossoming on the course.
18 holes, 18 souls bound together.
You know what I'm saying?
He is trying so hard to do the classic nice guy thing.
I'm not like most men, not like most men.
They become monkeys.
Me?
Nope.
Definitely not doing that.
I just love you.
I just love with you.
Do you know that?
I think you are absolutely beautiful.
And you have my heart.
I will actually die for you if you ask me to do so.
Did you know that?
Because I love you.
Why are you not reciprocating these feelings right now?
Why are we not going back and forth with this?
Do you not feel the same?
What did I do wrong?
Huh?
You hate me?
Oh, you hate me, do you?
OK.
Like that's exactly like the tone of this flirting
right here from this guy.
It's like the creepiest ris.
Now when I was initially watching this,
I saw something dangling from like his shirt.
I thought at first it was like a really big goatee.
But upon further inspection, it's not.
So then I thought this may have been like a skit or something
because it started to look like a mic, like a lav mic.
But when I blew it up and enhanced it,
like it was fucking CSI, it turns out it's sunglasses.
At least I'm almost 100% sure it's sunglasses
that he has on the collar here.
I'm pretty sure.
I don't think this is staged or anything.
It doesn't look like it.
And that isn't a mic.
If it wasn't mic, the audio would be far clearer.
It's pretty clear that it's coming from the phone
that she has in the cart.
But anyway, I just wanted to throw that out there
that I went through like a whole investigation
here to see what that fucking dangling thing was.
Are you doing cart?
Yes.
But I will tell you this.
If I do see you again, which I hope I do, I'm going to talk
to you more.
Having, I'm like being in your orbit.
I hope you are told on a daily basis that you are treasured.
Much as I hate to say this, I am going to miss you.
I want to enjoy every moment.
And I hate knowing that this moment is going to end.
We have beautiful golfing in front of me.
It's just, I have someone so beautiful in front of me
right now too.
I have become a puddle in my pants.
Excellent work, gentle sir.
Wow.
That was very smooth.
A lot to take in there.
A very strong finale.
The conclusion couldn't have been better.
He laments that their conversation has to end
because she needs to get back to work.
And you have occupied plenty of her time
with this song and dance.
But he wants to give a parting speech anyway.
I've really enjoyed our time together, ma'am.
If you could rate me five stars on Yelp for this conversation,
it'd be a lot to me.
Like, he's trying to accelerate on something.
And he's like, I really hope I see you again.
And if I do, fair warning.
I'm going to want to talk to you again.
Yeah.
I'm going to want to say hello again.
I'm going to want to come over and fucking bother you again.
Yes, I am.
It's just so hard to say goodbye.
It really sucks that these moments have to end.
Like time progresses.
It's kind of cringe, right?
I wish we could stay locked in this conversation forever.
I'm sure you do as well.
And it's just something you got to really stop
and smell the roses about.
Like, I got beautiful golfing in front of me here,
going 45 over parbed on the daily.
But I also have something beautiful right here.
You.
And, you know, I'd really like to kind of just stay
over here in this beauty, you know what I mean?
You're leaving?
Oh, okay.
No, no, no, yeah, okay, you're leaving?
All right.
Now, I think there is a strong lesson here.
A good takeaway for those watching at home.
Don't be like this guy.
Not just on the golf course, you know,
like this guy, he's fucking,
he's shanking the drives when it comes to flirting.
Like these are some really rough slices.
And this kind of tactic will be bad,
no matter where it is deployed here.
Like aggressively yelling compliments at a woman,
like to her face, that's just going to be perceived
as like a threat.
Like it is, as he said, dangerous.
Like that just seems dangerous
with this guy who comes up acting unhinged.
You're stunning.
Storning!
Agilirating!
Like it's weird.
It's on.
And also coupled with the fact that he is literally
impeding her ability to leave if she wants to,
like making it harder for her to flee the conversation,
not great, not the ideal circumstances to try and
have love blossom there.
So I would recommend not flirting in this manner
to anyone, anywhere, even outside of golf courses,
believe it or not.
But anyway, I just want to talk about this a little bit.
It had me pretty surprised here.
That's about it.
See ya.